Guide to the Frank Baker papers, 1641-2002 and undated, bulk 1740-1995 RL.00069
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1641-1999 and undated, 122 boxes
  - Subject Files Series: Alphabetical Files, Sequence I Subseries, 1641-1996 and undated, 58 boxes
    - Briggs, William, 1742, 1750 (Box 63)
      Contains photocopy/transcription of letter from Briggs to Charles Wesley, 1742 Nov. 22; contains photocopy of letter from Briggs to John Wesley, 1750 Apr. 5.
    - Brisco, Thomas, 1742, 1776, 1870 (Box 63)
      Contains transcription of letter from Brisco to Charles Wesley, 1760 Nov. 17.
    - Bristol, 1948-1958 (Box 63)
    - Bristol book steward, 1752, 1956, and undated (Box 63)
      Includes Baker's extensive notes and transcriptions of the original, held in the Frank Baker Collection of Wesleyana and British Methodism, Volumes Series. Note: formerly mis-attributed and cited as "Thomas Butts Diary, 1752-1754," which attribution FB disputes in these notes. Renamed in 2010 as "Bristol Steward's Diary, 1752-1754."
    - Bristol diarist, 1760s, 1779, 1785 (Box 63)
      Contains photocopy of the manuscript, "Texts of Sermons Preached by Wesley, Oddie, Davis, or others, 1764-1765." Also contains Baker's notes and tables of "Sermons preached in Bristol area by Meth. Preachers, 1764-65." Does not refer to the "Bristol Steward's Diary" (above), written a decade earlier. The term may possibly refer to the unknown transcriber of the "Bristol newspaper and letter transcriptions, 1743-1777 and undated," found in the Frank Baker Collection of Wesleyana and British Methodism, Writings and Addresses Series; or it may refer to yet a third unknown author in the Bristol area.
    - Bristol: General, 1780s, 1899-1948, 1966, undated (Box 64)
    - Bristol New Room, 1772-83, 1842, 1876, 1901-1905, 1921-1963, and undated, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - B.B.C. -- First Communion Broadcast, 1951 and undated (Box 64)
    - British Israelites, 1955 and undated (Box 64)
    - British Museum, 1946, 1954, and undated (Box 64)
    - Broadbent, John, 1779, 1787 (Box 64)
    - Brocas, Thomas, Some Diaries of Thomas Brocas, Salopian, 1785-1787, 1804-1818, and 1995 (Box 64)
      Typewritten transcription, approximately 150 pages, of the diaries of Thomas Brocas (1756-1818) of Shrewsbury. Detailed accounts of personal and local events as well as commentary on national political events, including the Napoleonic Wars.
    - Brontë Family, 1949-1951, 1965 and undated (Box 64)
    - Brook, Thomas and Brooke, Henry, undated (Box 64)
    - Broughton, Thomas, 1735-1737, undated (Box 64)
    - Brown, Isaac, John, and James, 1755-1759 (Box 64)
    - Bryant, Thomas, 1765, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Bucke, Emory Stevens, 1958-1959 (Box 64)
    - Buckinghams, 1943 (Box 64)
    - Buffon, Count de, Natural History, 1973, 1994, undated (Box 64)
    - Bull, William, undated (Box 64)
    - Bulmer, Agnes, 1840 and undated (Box 64)
    - Bunting, Jabez, 1810-1846 and undated (Box 64)
      Transcriptions, predominantly by FB, of twenty-eight Bunting letters from various collections. The most frequent recipient is Thomas Jackson; other recipients include John Beecham and Barnard Slater.
    - Bunting, T.P., undated (Box 64)
    - Bunyan, John, 1947 and undated (Box 64)
    - Burnett, George, 1782, 1950 (Box 64)
    - Burney Family, 1959-1960 and undated (Box 64)
    - Burials, undated (Box 64)
    - Bury, 1949-1952 and undated (Box 64)
    - Bury St. Edmunds, 1955-1958 (Box 64)
      Brief correspondence between Baker and J. Duncan; series of three pamphlets by Duncan, The Origins of the Free Churches in Bury St. Edmunds, 1955. These recount the history of Methodism in Bury St. Edmunds circa 1754-1880. Early years give many details of JW's visits to the area; an appendix, "Villages Missioned from Bury," outlines the spread of Methodism in this part of England.
    - Businessmen, Methodist, 1983 (Box 64)
    - Butterfield Collection, undated (Box 65)
    - Butterworth, Joseph; with FB manuscript, The Second Methodist M.P., undated (Box 65)
    - Byrom, John, 1773, 1940s (Box 65)
    - California, 1947 (Box 65)
    - Calvert, James, 1870, 1959 (Box 65)
    - Caldwell, John: Diary, 1768-1769 (Box 65)
    - Calkin, Homer, 1979 (Box 65)
    - Calvin, John, 1971 (Box 65)
    - Calvinistic Methodist Historical Society, (Welsh), 1939, 1959-1980, 3 folders (Box 65)
    - Cambridge, 1957, 1960, 1995 (Box 65)
    - Camp Meetings, 1958 (Box 65)
    - Canada, 1834-1973, and undated, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Canada, 1994-1995 (Box 65)
    - Canadian Methodist Historical Society, 1975-1977 and undated (Box 65)
    - Canadian Methodist Historical Society, 1992, 1995 (Box 65)
    - Card files--information folders, 1955-circa 1980 and undated, 4 folders (Box 65)
      Miscellaneous printed materials, including bibliographies and published articles, separated from their like-named card files in the Card Files Subseries. Includes articles by G. Lawton on concordances to JW's works, a list of Methodist letters, an index to a volume about Methodist Societies, and an index of JW's library.
    - Cardiff, (First Welsh Society), 1950, 1962 (Box 65)
    - Carlill, Thomas, 1780, 1791 (Box 65)
    - Carmina Quadragesimalia, 1723, 1748 (Box 65)
    - Carne, Joseph (Wesleyan Geologist), undated (Box 65)
    - Carteret, 1758 (Box 66)
    - Cartwright, Peter and Frances, 1976 (Box 66)
    - Case, Ernest, 1977, 1978 (Box 66)
    - Catechism, 1975 (Box 66)
    - Catholics, Roman, 1949, 1977, 1986 (Box 66)
    - Catlow, Jonathan, undated (Box 66)
    - Cayley, Cornelius, 1950 (Box 66)
    - Cennick, John -- FB: John Cennick A Handlist of His Writings, 1957-1958 (Box 66)
    - Cennick, John, 1718-89, 1955-76, 1989 (Box 66)
    - Cennick's Journals, 1753 (Box 66)
    - Centenary, 1984 (Box 66)
    - Chadwick, Samuel, 1960 (Box 66)
    - Chandler, Edward, 1744, 1786 (Box 66)
    - Channel Islands, 1753, 1779, 1785, 1947-1952 (Box 66)
    - Chapels, 1763, 1782, 1888-1906, 1932-1972, and undated (Box 66)
    - Chapels - Old, 1940-1959 and undated (Box 66)
    - Chap-books, 1889 (Box 66)
    - Chapmans, 1926, 1992 (Box 66)
    - Chapone family, 1736 (Box 66)
    - Charities - Joseph Rank Benevolent Fund, 1950 (Box 66)
    - Charity Schools, 1718, 1789, and undated (Box 66)
    - Charity: Sermons, 1759 (Box 66)
    - Charles Wesley Society, 1790, 1989-1996, and undated, 3 folders (Box 67)
    - Charnock, Stephen, 1994 (Box 67)
    - Charterhouse, 1710, 1816, 1937, 1950, 1978 and undated (Box 67)
    - Check, Nicholas Mosley, 1976, 1984, 1988 (Box 67)
    - Chelmsford, 1947 (Box 67)
    - Cheshire, 1788, 1839, 1847, 1912, 1945-1958, 1983 (Box 67)
      Includes handwritten copy of 1839 letter of Sarah Byrom, aged 70, a narrative of her memories of the early days of Methodism in Booth Bank, Manchester Circuit, and her grandfather's interactions with the Wesleys.
    - Cheyne, Dr. George, undated (Box 67)
    - Chingford Hatch, 1832, 1947 (Box 67)
    - Children, 1950 and undated (Box 67)
    - Choirs, 1939, 1958, and undated (Box 67)
    - Christian Advocate, 1946-1947 (Box 67)
    - Christian history, 1743-1745, 1917-1925, 1951-1966, 1977 and undated (Box 67)
    - Christian Perfection, 1970, 1985 (Box 67)
    - Christmas - Conference, 1959, 1982 (Box 67)
    - Christmas, 1907 (Box 67)
    - Christmas, 1930-1978, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 67)
    - Christmas, 1930-1978, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 68)
    - Church History - Early, 1951 (Box 68)
    - Church of England, undated (Box 68)
    - Church, William, undated (Box 68)
    - Churches (cf. Chapels), 1956 and undated (Box 68)
    - Churchey, Walter, 1770-1791, 1849, 1971-1974 (Box 68)
    - Circuit Plans, 1784, 1790, 1818, 1978, 1988 (Box 68)
    - Circuits, 1773-1774, 1785-1786, 1841, 1949, 1995-1996, and undated (Box 68)
    - Clark, Elmer T., 1938, 1947-1956, 1963 and undated (Box 68)
    - Clark, George, circa 1740s-1780s (Box 68)
    - Clarke, Adam, 1785-1789, 1799, 1805-1827, 1850, 1879, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Clarke, Adam, 1795-1836, 1847, 1851, 1884, 1934, 1954-1958, and undated (Box 68)
    - Class Tickets: Wright Collection, 1742-1791 (Box 68)
    - Classical Dress, undated (Box 68)
    - Classical Translations, 1830 and undated (Box 68)
    - Clayton, Marshall and family, 1992-1993 and undated (Box 68)
    - Clayton, Rev. John, 1731-1739, 1755, and undated (Box 68)
    - Cleethorpes, 1759-1761, 1803, 1847-1859, 1936, 1947-1958, 1979, and undated (Box 68)
    - Clegg, James, 1709-1754 (Box 69)
    - Clergy lists, Circa 1770s-1790s (Box 69)
    - Clergy, 1662, 1737, 1789, 1872-1876, and undated (Box 69)
    - Cliff College, undated (Box 69)
    - Clowes, William, 1950-1954 and undated (Box 69)
    - CME Church, 1985 (Box 69)
    - Coffee, 1891, 1933, 1987, and undated (Box 69)
    - Coke, Thomas - Letters, 1781-1814, 1839. 1847, 1948, 1963, 1981 (Box 69)
    - Coke, Thomas (Vickers), 1963-1964 and undated (Box 69)
    - Coke, Thomas--"Catalog of the Thomas Coke Papers," Methodist Archives Research Centre, John Rylands University of Manchester, 1991 (Box 69)
    - Coke, Thomas, 1773, 1786, 1793-1798, 1805, 1810-1813, 1851, 1859, 1936-1961, 1967-1971, 1988, and undated, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - Cokesbury College, 1969 (Box 69)
    - Colbeck, Thomas, 1755-1757, 1779, and undated (Box 69)
    - Colbert, William, 1790-1791, 1980 (Box 69)
    - Cole, Reverend William, and Joseph, 1784, 1931 (Box 69)
    - Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1948, 1952, 1955 (Box 69)
    - Coles, George, 1958 (Box 69)
    - Colet, John Annesley, 1791, 1989 (Box 69)
    - Collections - Church Donations, 1948 and undated (Box 69)
    - Collins, Brian Bury, 1779, 1786 (Box 69)
    - Comenius - Influence on JW, 1679, 1989 (Box 69)
    - Commando Campaigns, 1947-1949 and undated, 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Condy, Richard, 1989 and undated (Box 70)
    - Confirmation, 1949, 1963, 1975, and undated (Box 70)
    - Congregationalists, 1948, 1958 (Box 70)
    - Conversion, 1979 and undated (Box 70)
    - Conyers, Rev. Dr. Richard, 1919 (Box 70)
    - Cook, 1773-1774, 1943 (Box 70)
    - Cooper, Thomas and Ezekiel, 1790-1791, 1872 (Box 70)
    - Cooper, Thomas, 1788, 1819, 1835, 1995-1996, and undated (Box 70)
      Correspondence and photocopy of transcript of suspected JW ALS: Wesley, John, to Thomas Cooper, 1788 Sept. 22.; includes draft of Baker's article, Probing a Wesley Letter.
    - Copyright, 1968-1981 and undated (Box 70)
    - Copyright: John Wesley, copyright, and piracy, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Coram, Thomas, 1951 (Box 70)
    - Corderoy, 1938, 1959 (Box 70)
    - Cork, 1747-1750, 1948,1952, and undated (Box 70)
    - Cornwall, 1879-1885, 1909, 1946-1992, and undated, 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Costerdine, Robert, 1779, 1814, 1935 (Box 70)
    - Costume, 1742, 1803, 1951, undated (Box 70)
    - Coughlan, Lawrence, 1776, 1785, 1949, 1989, undated (Box 70)
    - Country Life, 1947 (Box 70)
    - Coussins, Jonathan, 1771-1785, 1806, 1825, 1994, and undated (Box 71)
    - Covenant Service, 1969-1986, undated (Box 71)
    - Covenant, 1949, 1955, undated (Box 71)
    - Coventry, 1947-1953 (Box 71)
    - Cownley, Joseph, 1760-1794, 1988 (Box 71)
      Includes Baker's transcriptions of seven Cownley letters to Charles Wesley, Joseph Benson, and Christopher Hopper.
    - Cowper, William, 1950-51, 1970 (Box 71)
    - Creighton, James, 1778, 1785, 1794-1810, 1815, 1952, and undated (Box 71)
    - Cricket, 1951 (Box 71)
    - Crook, Henry John, 1747-1797, 1808, 1845, and undated (Box 71)
    - Crosby Collection, 1966-1967, undated (Box 71)
    - Crosby, Sarah, 1760-1780, 1806, 1862, 1886, and undated (Box 71)
    - Cross Stone Church, undated (Box 71)
    - Crosse, John, 1784-1815 (Box 71)
    - Crouch, Thomas, 1738-1742 (Box 71)
    - Crowther Family, 1824, 1869, 1926 (Box 71)
    - Cruden, Alexander, 1934, 1962 (Box 71)
    - Cudworth, William, 1745, 1759, 1969, and undated (Box 71)
    - Cumberland, 1951 (Box 71)
    - Cumbers, Frank, 1960-1985 (Box 71)
    - Cussons, George, 1779, 1875 (Box 71)
    - Dale, Margaret, Ann, Mary, etc., 1908 and undated (Box 71)
    - Dales Circuit, 1773-1774, 1788, and undated (Box 71)
    - Dancing, undated (Box 71)
    - Darney, William, 1741-1751, 1766, 1947-1961, 1978 (Box 71)
    - Dartmouth, Lord, 1781, 1950, undated (Box 72)
    - Dates, Dating: Dendochronology, 1994 and undated (Box 72)
    - Davies, Samuel--FB correspondence and notes, printed material, 1765, 1879, 1966-1972, and undated (Box 72)
      Also includes typed transcription of M. Davis letter to Charles Wesley, 1765 Aug. 25.
    - Davis, John--FB notes, undated (Box 72)
      For possibly related material, see also Frank Baker Collection of Wesleyana and British Methodism, "Thunders & lightenings & bolts of his wrath are not requisite..."
    - Deacon, Thomas, 1786, undated (Box 72)
    - Deafness and Hearing Aids, 1934-1949 and undated (Box 72)
    - Death, undated (Box 72)
    - Defoe, 1927, 1937, and undated (Box 72)
    - Delamotte Family, 1735, 1956-1965, 1993 (Box 72)
    - Deptford, 1740-1790, 1945, 1957 (Box 72)
    - Derby, 1895, 1901, 1923, 1947-1950, and undated (Box 72)
    - Designs, undated (Box 72)
    - Devon, 1698, 1959, 1965 (Box 72)
    - Diaries, 1756-1764, 1925, 1930, 1944, 1948 (Box 72)
    - Dickens, John, 1949, 1959-1960, 1979, and undated (Box 72)
    - Dickenson, Peard, 1803, 1874, and undated (Box 72)
    - Dictionaries: Notes on Wesley's, 1957 (Box 72)
    - Dillon, Rev. Richard, 1785 (Box 72)
    - Dioceses, 1727-1786, 1900 (Box 72)
    - Directories, Kelly's, 1954 (Box 72)
    - Disciplines, 1963-1965 and undated (Box 72)
    - Dissenters' Certificates, 1745, 1787, 1945, 1949, 1960, 1966, 1990, and undated (Box 72)
    - Dissertations and Theses, 1963, 1970-1977, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Distribution of Methodism, 1950 (Box 72)
    - District Synods, 1791-1831, 1865, 1949 (Box 72)
    - Dixon, James, 1825 (Box 72)
    - Doctrinal Tracts, 1831, 1963-1964, 1972, 1986, and undated (Box 72)
    - Doctrine, 1828-1829, 1938-1956, and undated (Box 72)
    - Doddridge, Mary, 1796, 1951-1952, 1970-1972 (Box 72)
    - Dodsley, Robert, 1744, 1983, and undated (Box 72)
    - Dodsworth Bequest, 1750-1781, 1946, 1949, and undated (Box 72)
    - Domesday Book, undated (Box 72)
    - Dornford, 1785-1787, 1794, 1809, 1911, 1958 (Box 72)
    - Dorset, 1950-1952 (Box 72)
    - Downes, John, 1747-1763 and 1953 (Box 72)
    - Downing, Rev. George, 1758 (Box 72)
    - Drew, Samuel, 1820-1828, 1891 and undated (Box 73)
    - Drinking, JW's views on, 1970 (Box 73)
    - Dromgoole, Edward, 1974, 1981 and undated (Box 73)
    - Drummond's Visit, 1747, 1764, 1933, 1978, and undated (Box 73)
    - Dryden, John, 1866 (Box 73)
    - Dublin Moravians and Methodists, 1760, 1783, 1980-1981, and undated (Box 73)
    - Dublin, 1829, 1898, 1925, 1941-1949, and undated (Box 73)
    - Duke, William, 1774-1776, 1986, and undated (Box 73)
    - Dunton, John, 1951 (Box 73)
    - Durbin, Henry, 1785 (Box 73)
    - Durham, U.K., 1744, 1939, 1947-1952, 1959, and undated (Box 73)
    - Dyer, William, 1952 and undated (Box 73)
    - Dyson, 1859, 1948 (Box 73)
    - Earthquakes, 1941-1950, 1959 (Box 73)
    - Easter, 1949 (Box 73)
    - Easterbrook, Joseph, 1786-1790 (Box 73)
    - Eastwood, J., 1764 (Box 73)
    - Economy (English), 1993 (Box 73)
    - Ecumenical Movement, 1950 (Box 73)
    - Edinburgh -- Samuel Rogal: John Wesley at Edinburgh: 1751-1790, 1978 and undated (Box 73)
    - Edmondson, Jonathan and Allen, 1813, 1822, 1834, 1949 (Box 73)
    - Education, 1807, 1844, 1855, 1877-1879, 1945-1960, 1967, 1977, 1982-1983, and undated, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Education, undated (Box 73)
    - Edwards, John, 1777, 1974 (Box 73)
    - Edwards, Maldwyn, 1947-1948 (Box 73)
    - Egmont, Earl of, 1920 (Box 73)
    - Eighteenth Century Church History, undated (Box 73)
    - Eighteenth Century History, British, undated (Box 73)
    - Eighteenth Century Social Background, 1904, 1926, 1932, 1935 (Box 73)
    - Eland, 1960 (Box 73)
    - Embury, Philip, 1963 (Box 73)
    - Emigration, 1947 (Box 73)
    - Emory, John, 1964 (Box 73)
    - Enclosures, 1936 (Box 73)
    - English Ecumenical Conference Tours, 1950-1951 (Box 74)
    - Engravings, 1951, 1975 (Box 74)
    - Entwisle, Joseph--FB transcriptions of letters to George Marsden, Jabez Bunting, James Everett, and others, 1802-1803, 1819-1840 (Box 74)
    - Ephraem Syrus, 1989 (Box 74)
    - Episcopacy, 1976 (Box 74)
    - Epworth Old Rectory Management Committee, 1954-1960 and undated, 2 folders (Box 74)
    - Epworth, 1700, 1808, 1857, 1879, 1905, 1936-1965, 1984, 1987, 1990, and undated, 2 folders (Box 74)
      "Escape of John Wesley from the Fire" (circa 1879?)
    - Epworth, 1851, 1957, 1962, and undated (Box 74)
    - Erasmus, 1948, 1956, 1963 (Box 74)
    - Erskine, Richard, 1834, 1956-1958 (Box 74)
    - Essex, 1951-1957 (Box 74)
    - Ethnic Groups in the United States, 1981 (Box 74)
    - Europe, Methodism in, 1979 and undated (Box 74)
    - Evangelical Biography, 1995 (Box 74)
    - Evangelical Magazine, 1793 (Box 75)
    - Evangelical Magazine, 1793-1817 (Box 75)
    - Evangelicals, 1757-1763, 1951-1952 (Box 75)
    - Evangelism, 1950-1958, 1967, and undated (Box 75)
    - Evans, 1808, 1947, and undated (Box 75)
    - Evans, James, 1954-1971 and undated, 5 folders (Box 75)
      Contains book-length biographical manuscript and drafts of articles on James Evans by Frank Baker.
    - Everett, James, 1753-1849 (Box 76)
    - Evolution, 1954 (Box 76)
    - Exhibitions, 1932, 1946-1958, and undated (Box 76)
      JW Bookmark
    - Exhorters, 1951 (Box 76)
    - Faculty, 1971 and undated (Box 76)
    - Fasting, 1982 (Box 76)
    - Fellowship of the Kingdom, Fraternals, F.K. Retreats, etc., 1946-1958 and undated (Box 76)
    - Fellowship, 1957-1958 (Box 76)
    - Fenwick, Michael John, 1793 (Box 76)
    - Fernando Po, 1970 (Box 76)
    - Festival, Circuit, 1951, 1957, and undated (Box 76)
    - Fielden, Fielding, 1948-1951, 1956 (Box 76)
    - Fieldhouse, 1951 (Box 76)
    - Finance, 1885-1886, 1937 and 1953 (Box 76)
    - Fire, 1785, 1957 (Box 76)
    - Fisher Collection, 1937 (Box 76)
    - Fitzgerald, Lady Mary, undated (Box 76)
    - Flash, Flashmen, 1795, 1861-1877, 1946 (Box 76)
    - Flesher, John, 1825-1826 (Box 76)
    - Fletcher, John, 1760-1764, 1772-1774, 1777, 1836, 1940-1961, 1979 and undated, Folders 1-2 of 5 (Box 76)
      Correspondence between Baker and other scholars on Fletcher letters and possible edition of Fletcher's works; photocopies and transcriptions of Fletcher letters; Fletcher portraits; article by Barry Williamson, "The Spilsbury Portrait of John Fletcher," 1989; photocopies of printed material by or about Fletcher, dating to the late 1700s.
    - Fletcher, John, 1760-1764, 1772-1774, 1777, 1836, 1940-1961, 1979 and undated, Folders 3-5 of 5 (Box 77)
    - Fletcher, Mary (Bosanquet), 1762-1773, 1816, 1847, 1862, 1988, and undated (Box 77)
    - Fletcher, Mary (Bosanquet)--anonymous letter to Mrs. Fletcher, 1785, 1995 (Box 77)
    - Fo(r)ester, 1850, 1951 (Box 77)
    - Foot, Isaac, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Ford, Dr. Thomas, 1773 (Box 77)
    - Fothergill, Anthony, 1953 and undated (Box 77)
    - France, 1947-1952, 1969, and undated (Box 77)
    - Franklin, Benjamin and Timothy of Charleston (Wesley's Printer), 1959, 1972 (Box 77)
    - Franks, Samuel, 1773 (Box 77)
    - Free Church Federal Council, Free Methodists, 1949-1951, 1984 (Box 77)
    - Freemasons, 1949-1963 and undated (Box 77)
    - Fry, Elizabeth, John, and Joseph, 1749, 1791, and 1950-1952 (Box 77)
    - Funerals, 1821, 1944-1952, 1983, and undated (Box 77)
    - Furley, 1762, 1866 (Box 77)
    - Furly, Samuel, 1764 (Box 77)
    - Gallatin Family, 1791 (Box 77)
    - Galloway, Joseph, 1781, 1942 and 1993 (Box 77)
    - Gamble, Robert, 1788, 1951 and undated (Box 77)
    - Gambling, Gaming, 1944, 1953, and undated (Box 77)
    - Gambold, Rev. John, 1740, 1814, and 1865 (Box 78)
    - Garber, Bishop Paul Neff, 1949-1950, 1972-1974, and undated (Box 78)
    - Garrett, Charles, 1882-1893 and undated (Box 78)
    - Garrettson, Freeborn, 1794, 1829 (Box 78)
    - Gatch, Philip, 1976 (Box 78)
    - Gateshead, 1771 (Box 78)
    - Gaulter, John, 1819 and undated (Box 78)
    - Gaussen, M., 1759 (Box 78)
    - Gell, Robert, 1777, 1970 (Box 78)
    - Genealogists, Society of, 1989-1995 (Box 78)
    - Genealogy, 1944-1956, 1965, 1981, and undated (Box 78)
    - General Fund, undated (Box 78)
    - George, Raymond, 1993-1994 (Box 78)
    - Georgia, Willie Snow Ethridge Strange Fires: The True Story of John Wesley's Love Affair in Georgia, 1971, 1978 (Box 78)
    - Georgia Pro, 1735-1738 (Box 78)
    - Georgia Settlers, 1949, 1991 (Box 78)
    - Georgia, 1846, 1927, 1934, 1947-1963, 1970-1979, 1989, and undated, 2 folders (Box 78)
    - Georgia, 1960-1976 and undated (Box 79)
    - Georgia, Fredrica Area, 1956-1960, 1979 and undated (Box 79)
    - Georgia, Savannah, 1807, 1955-1963, 1971-1974, 1981-1985, and undated (Box 79)
    - Gerdes, Egon, 1971-1975 (Box 79)
    - German Script, 1977 (Box 79)
    - Germany, 1946-2002 and undated, 7 folders (Box 79)
      Folders 1-2 contain general research materials on Methodism in Germany. Folders 3-7 contain correspondence, photographs, and writings regarding the Baker family's acquaintance and ongoing relationship with a group of German prisoners-of-war, who were held at Camp Norton when the Bakers lived in Warsop, England, circa 1947. Additional background information about these events can be found in a 2002 letter from the Bakers' daughter Enid Hickingbotham, filed in the correspondence folder here, and in the undated address by Nellie Baker, "Make Us Builders of Peace." The folders also include two music manuscripts by Heinrich Heun from 1947 and 1948, and an article by Ilsabe Halves, Wir Beide Hand in Hand, 1995
    - Ghana: Kwaku, 1983-1984 (Box 80)
    - Gibbons, Thomas, undated (Box 80)
    - Gibraltar, 1827-1828, 1839, 1955-1957, 1989, and undated (Box 80)
    - Gibson, Edmund, undated (Box 80)
    - Gilbert Family and West Indies, 1760, 1950, 1959-1961, 1984-1985, and undated (Box 80)
    - Gill, John and Judith, undated (Box 80)
    - Gillies, Dr. John, undated (Box 80)
    - Gilpin, Bernard, 1973 (Box 80)
    - Glascott, Cradock and Thomas, 1965 (Box 80)
    - Glass, Writing on, 1957 (Box 80)
    - Glendinning, William, 1983 (Box 80)
    - Gloucestershire, 1950 (Box 80)
    - Godbold, Albea, 1964 (Box 80)
    - Goodwin, John, 1778 (Box 80)
    - Gordon, Alexander, 1995 (Box 80)
    - Gospel Magazine, 1940-1946 (Box 80)
    - Graces, undated (Box 80)
    - Granville, Ann and Mary, undated (Box 80)
    - Graves, Richard, 1970 (Box 80)
    - Great Holiness Classics, 1981-1987 (Box 80)
    - Greek, 1980 and undated (Box 80)
    - Green Hill, 1969 (Box 80)
    - Green, Richard, Charles, Robert, 1767-1905 and undated (Box 80)
    - Greenwood, 1758-1783 (Box 80)
    - Griffith, Walter, 1808, 1810 (Box 80)
    - Grimaldi, Alexander, 1957 (Box 80)
    - Grimsby, 1743, 1782, 1824-1858, 1951-1957, and undated (Box 80)
    - Grindrod, Edmund, 1820-1839 (Box 80)
    - Gumley, 1978 (Box 80)
    - Gush, William, 1957 (Box 80)
    - Gutteridge, Leslie, 1967-1973 (Box 80)
    - Gwynne Family, 1841, 1949-1972 (Box 80)
    - Gwynne, Marmaduke, 1741-1749 (Box 80)
    - Gwynne, Mrs. Sarah, 1749 (Box 80)
    - Gwynne, Rebecca, 1749, 1752, 1770, 1781 (Box 80)
    - Haliburton, Thomas, 1969 and undated (Box 81)
    - Halifax, 1749, 1786, 1842, 1928-1952, and undated (Box 81)
    - Hall Collection, 1791-1838, 1856, 1945, 1949 (Box 81)
    - Hall, Westley, 1734-1735, 1742, 1747, 1770, 1950 (Box 81)
    - Hallam, John, 1951 (Box 81)
    - Hamilton, Eliza James, 1810 (Box 81)
    - Hamilton, James, 1774-1791, 1829-1838, and undated (Box 81)
    - Hammet, William, 1948 (Box 81)
    - Hampshire, 1948 (Box 81)
    - Hanby, Thomas, 1787, 1789 (Box 81)